Guide to the Stanford University, Undergraduate Advising Center, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Undergraduate Advising Center, records
circa 1965-2003
SC0316
Stanford University. Undergraduate Advising Center.
32 Linear feet
Office files regarding freshman and sophomore special seminars, c. 1965-83; chron files, 1978 and 1981-84; records pertaining to the senior survey, 1972-81; and other administrative records, 1996-2003.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Office files regarding freshman and sophomore special seminars, c. 1965-83; chron files, 1978 and 1981-84; records pertaining to the senior survey, 1972-81; and other administrative records, 1996-2003.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Academic Information Center.; Stanford University. Undergraduate Advising Center.; Advising.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1994-102
  - Senior Survey results for pre-med students, 1972-1984 (Box 1)
  - Senior Survey results for pre-law and pre-business students, 1980-1984 (Box 2)
  - Senior Survey results, 1971-1979 (bound together, binding broken) (Box 2)
  - Senior Survey results, 1975-1979 (bound together) (Box 2)
  - Course Abstracts, Fall 1984/85 (Box 2)
  - Course Abstracts, Winter 1984/85 (Box 2)
  - Course Abstracts, Spring 1984/85 (Box 2)
  - Undergraduate Advising Center Annual Report 1987 (Box 2)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-004
  - Aspire Consulting 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Budget 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Budget 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gibbs, Stanford Undergraduate Education in the 70s: A Call for Educating the Whole Person 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guide for Grad Schools (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - IDM Self-study Report 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - John Bravman Presentation 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lori White Speeches 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Orientation 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Orientation 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Orientation Review 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Planning 2002 (1 of 3) 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Planning 2002 (2 of 3) 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Planning 2002 (3 of 3) 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Planning Committee 2000-01 (1 of 4) 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Planning Committee 2000-01 (2 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Planning Committee 2000-01 (3 of 4) 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Planning Committee 2000-01 (4 of 4) 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Planning Meeting 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - President's Scholars 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Promotions/Marketing 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Publications Current (1 of 2) 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Publications Current (2 of 2) 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - RPIG 1998 (Residential Programming Implementation Group) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - RPIG Upperclass 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Report On the Advising Task Force 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Retreat 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Retreat 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Retreat #2 (Backup) 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Retreat July 1999 Douglas House (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Scrap Book Press Releases 1991 1992 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Staff Meeting 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Staff Roles w/in UAC 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Plan 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Strategic Planning 1997-98 (1 of 3) 1987 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Strategic Planning 1997-98 (2 of 3) 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Planning 1997-98 (3 of 3) 1985 1987 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee On Academic Environment 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - UAC Employee Support Group 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - UAC: Freshman Advising at Stanford Univ. 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - UAC Planning Comm. Notes (1 of 2) 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - UAC Planning Comm. Notes (2 of 2) 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - UAC Plans/Strategies 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - UAC Reorganization 1997-98 (1 of 2) 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - UAC Reorganization 1997-98 (2 of 2) 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - UAC Staff Survey 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - UAC Strategic Plan 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Update On Undergrad. Advising 2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - V. Prov. U.E. Meeting Notes 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Vice Provost for U.E. 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Women's Center 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Working Groups 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)